Since 2001 and the Clearstream-gate, there has been a scandal every year
concerning tax evasion and tax trafficking.
The truth is that tax evasion is written in the genetic code of the European Union,
that facilitates tax trafficking.
Article163 forbids tax harmonization, which amounts to encouraging the lowest bid.
Article 63 facilitates all the transactions and forbids a limit to the transactions between countries.
The fact that this system is legal is the reason why you succeeded in electing
the person that is responsible for these scandals as President of the European Commission.
And after two sessions of the parliamentary commission, you still haven't found anything.
But on April 26th, the two whistleblowers that revealed this scandal will be judged.
They face 10 years' imprisonment and 1M euros fine.
In these conditions, the Luxleaks-gate repeats itself with the Panama Papers.
The French bank Société Générale was under ECB control
while it was opening offshore companies.
The head of the company committed perjury before French Members of Parliament,
but I'm the one who is prosecuted for defamation!
Since your plans are useless, the only you have one thing to do
is to protect whistleblowers. They are severely punished because they did us a service.